Guide to the Human sexuality-related videorecordings,1990-2013.
Human sexuality-related videorecordings,1990-2013
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Human sexuality-related videorecordings, 1990-2013.
7713
N/A
4.3 cubic feet.
Videocassettes, DVDs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Videorecorded productions relating to Human Sexuality.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Videorecorded productions relating to Human Sexuality.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videorecordings.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Safer Sex
Series II. Erotica
Series III. Couples and Relationships
Series IV. Gender and Transgender
Series V. Documentaries, Movies, and Television Programming
Series VI. Miscellaneous
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Safer Sex
  - A Gay Man's Safe Sex Guide, V-658 (Box 1)
  - She's Safe!, V-671 (Box 2)
  - The Gay Man's Guide to Safer Sex, 1993; V-682 (Box 3)
    Gift of Mariposa
  - Safer Sex Shorts, V-684 (Box 3)
  - What Next: A Story of Sex in the 80's, V-685 (Box 3)
  - Current Flow, V-687 (Box 3)
  - Making the Man: A Young Man's Guide to Safer Sex, DVD-4 (Box 4)
- Series II. Erotica
  - Sluts & Goddesses Video Workshop, 1992; V-651 (Box 1)
  - Suburban Dykes, 1998; V-653 (Box 1)
  - AMG: The Fantasy Factory, V-655 (Box 1)
  - AMG: The Fantasy Factory Revisited, V-656 (Box 1)
  - AMG: A Third Visit, V-657 (Box 1)
  - Kama Sutra of Gay Sex, V-666 (Box 2)
  - Advocate Men Live!, V-675 (Box 2)
  - Advocate Men Live! 2, V-676 (Box 2)
  - Advocate Men Live! 3, V-677 (Box 3)
  - Advocate Men Live! 4, V-678 (Box 3)
  - "Big Buddies" Advocate Men Live! 6, V-679 (Box 3)
  - Do Me Evil, 1980; V-681 (Box 3)
  - Better Sex Video Series, 1992; V-881 - V-883 (Box 4)
  - Worst Boy in Town, 1996; V-1105 (Box 4)
  - Sebastian, 1996; V-1111 (Box 4)
  - Hamam, the Turkish Bath, 2000; V-1112 (Box 4)
  - Sacerdote, V-1113 (Box 4)
  - Under Heat, 1998; V-1114 (Box 4)
  - Sugar Sweet, 2003; DVD-2 (Box 4)
  - I Wish You Would: 5 Sizzling Lesbian Fantasies, DVD-3 (Box 4)
  - Alley Katt, 2001; DVD-24 (Box 4)
  - Trespass [3 disks], 2001/2002; DVD-28 (Box 4)
  - John Homes Goes Gay, 2002; DVD-29 (Box 4)
  - All Night Long, 2001; DVD-53 (Box 6)
  - Exposed: the Making of a Legend, 2006; DVD-54 (Box 6)
  - Making It Huge, pre-1995; DVD-55 (Box 6)
  - All The Rage, 2003; DVD-216 (Box 6)
  - Adam and Eve, V-6068 (Box 7)
  - Analicious, 1998; V-6069 (Box 7)
  - As Time Goes Bi..., V-6071 (Box 7)
  - Bad Boys - Volume 3, V-6072 (Box 7)
  - Bad Boys - Volume 30, V-6073 (Box 7)
  - Bad Boys of Berlin, V-6074 (Box 7)
  - Bad Habits, V-6075 (Box 7)
  - Best of Colt 4, 1986; V-6076 (Box 7)
  - Best of Buckshot - Part 1, 1984; V-6077 (Box 7)
  - Brian's Boys, 1990; V-6078 (Box 7)
  - Bronze, 1991; V-6079 (Box 7)
  - Buckshot - Pumping Fever, 1993; V-6080 (Box 7)
  - Bi-Guy, 1990; V-6081 (Box 7)
  - Black and Ready, V-6082 (Box 7)
  - Black Male, 1990; V-6083 (Box 7)
  - California Big Hunks, 1985; V-6084 (Box 7)
  - Caribbean Cruising, 1990; V-6085 (Box 7)
  - Celebration, 1986; V-6086 (Box 7)
  - Class Reunion, 1989; V-6070 (Box 7)
  - Cowpokin' Cocksuckers, V-6087 (Box 7)
  - Double Exposure, 1987; V-6088 (Box 7)
  - Dynamite Dicks and Bubble Buns, 1993; V-6089 (Box 7)
  - Erotikus... A History of the Gay Movies, V-6090 (Box 7)
  - European "High Lites", V-6091 (Box 7)
  - Eyes of a Stranger, V-6092 (Box 7)
  - French Kiss, V-6093 (Box 7)
  - Flashbacks, V-6094 (Box 7)
  - The Greek In Me, V-6095 (Box 7)
  - Heatstroke, V-6096 (Box 7)
  - Home All Alone/ Liberation, 1992; V-6097 (Box 7)
  - H Stroke #5 Deep Fantasies, V-6098 (Box 7)
  - Hung and Dangerous/Cinderella, 1991; V-6099 (Box 7)
  - Hung Studs - Volume 3, 1991; V-6100 (Box 7)
  - Hunks in Hedonism, V-6101 (Box 7)
  - International Guide to the Fine Art of Fellatio, 1989; V-6102 (Box 7)
  - In the End Zone, 1989; V-6103 (Box 7)
  - Island Fever, 1990; V-6104 (Box 7)
  - It's Raining Dicks, 1993; V-6105 (Box 7)
  - Ladies Night Out, 1983; V-6106 (Box 8)
  - LA Plays Itself and Sex Garage, 1972; V-6107 (Box 8)
  - Latino Nights, V-6108 (Box 8)
  - Legends of Kama Sutra, V-6109 (Box 8)
  - Let Me Be Your Loverboy, V-6110 (Box 8)
  - Life Guard/ His, 1985; V-6111 (Box 8)
  - Lucky 7, V-6112 (Box 8)
  - Male Erotic, 1992; V-6113 (Box 8)
  - Man O' Man, V-6114 (Box 8)
  - Manpower Australia, 1993; V-6115 (Box 8)
  - Maximum Strength Disrobics, 1987; V-6116 (Box 8)
  - Morning Music, 1996; V-6117 (Box 8)
  - The Nasty Groove, 1992; V-6118 (Box 8)
  - Once Upon a Time, V-6119 (Box 8)
  - One, Two, Three, V-6120 (Box 8)
  - Party Hard!, V-6121 (Box 8)
  - Picture Perfect, 1991; V-6122 (Box 8)
  - Preview #6, 1992; V-6123 (Box 8)
  - The Producer, V-6124 (Box 8)
  - Queens of Thailand, 1991; V-6125 (Box 8)
  - Raw Footage, V-6126 (Box 8)
  - The Rites of Summer, V-6127 (Box 8)
  - The Rodz, V-6128 (Box 8)
  - Screw Ups, V-6129 (Box 8)
  - Seattle Sea Hunks, V-6130 (Box 8)
  - Sensual Men, 1991; V-6131 (Box 8)
  - Sex Drive/ Paladin, 1989; V-6132 (Box 8)
  - Steel Garters/Catalina, 1992; V-6133 (Box 8)
  - Strictly For Ladies Only, 1988; V-6134 (Box 8)
  - Sunstroke, 1989; V-6135 (Box 8)
  - Supermen (Advocate Men), 1995; V-6136 (Box 8)
  - Super Models of Advocate Men, V-6137 (Box 8)
  - Top Models, V-6138 (Box 8)
  - Tough Competition, V-6139 (Box 8)
  - X-tra Large, V-6140 (Box 8)
  - XXX - European Video - Title No. 516, V-6141 (Box 8)
  - Behind the Eight Ball, V-6143 (Box 9)
  - Bi and Kinky- Special, 1996; V-6144 (Box 9)
  - Big and Thick, 1995; V-6145 (Box 9)
  - The French Erection, V-6146 (Box 9)
  - Grid Iron, V-6147 (Box 9)
  - Hard to Be Good, 1989; V-6148 (Box 9)
  - Hologram, V-6149 (Box 9)
  - Hunk Hunt, 1996; V-6150 (Box 9)
  - Kinky Leather, 1995; V-6151 (Box 9)
  - Man Alone, V-6152 (Box 9)
  - Mannequin Man, 1995; V-6153 (Box 9)
  - Move Over Johnny, 1985; V-6154 (Box 9)
  - Seduction IV, 1989; V-6155 (Box 9)
  - Shower Fantasies, 1991; V-6156 (Box 9)
  - Slammer- The Ultimate Wrestling Video, 1995; V-6157 (Box 9)
  - Slave to Cock, 1995; V-6158 (Box 9)
  - Slither, 1996; V-6159 (Box 9)
  - Spokes, 1984; V-6160 (Box 9)
  - Toys In Us, 1995; V-6161 (Box 9)
  - V8, 1991; V-6162 (Box 9)
  - Bonanza's Booty Bang, 2005; DVD-810 (Box 6)
  - Spanish Fly Honeys, 2005; DVD-811 (Box 6)
  - Lukas in Love, part 1, DVD-845 (Box 6)
  - Lukas in Love, part 2, DVD-846 (Box 6)
  - Greek Holiday, DVD-847 (Box 6)
  - The Private Life of Tim Hamilton, DVD-848 (Box 6)
  - Descent, 2000; DVD-902 (Box 6)
  - Big & Thick, 2004; DVD-903 (Box 6)
- Series III. Couples and Relationships
  - The Male Couple Video, 1985; V-683 (Box 3)
  - Male Couples Facing AIDS, V-686 (Box 3)
  - All American Boys, pre-1995; DVD-52 (Box 4)
  - The Consequence, 2006; DVD-59 (Box 4)
  - Separate Peace, 2004; DVD-213 (Box 6)
  - Giorni, 2002; DVD-215 (Box 6)
  - Straightman, 2002; DVD-217 (Box 6)
  - Cock & Bull Story, DVD-218 (Box 6)
  - Doubt, 2003, 2005; DVD-219 (Box 6)
  - Beach Café, 2001; DVD-220 (Box 6)
- Series IV. Gender and Transgender
  - Linda Les & Annie, V-660 (Box 1)
  - Gender 101, 1993; V-661 (Box 1)
  - Husbands and Wives, Best Friends and Lovers, 1991; V-663 (Box 1)
  - What Sex Am I?, V-688 (Box 3)
  - La Cage Aux Folles, with English Subtitles, V-689 (Box 3)
  - Buck Angel's Sexing The Transman, volume 1 and 3, DVD-1473, DVD-1474 (Box 6)
- Series V. Documentaries, Movies, and Television Programming
  - We are here to stay!!!, 1990; V-652 (Box 1)
  - TimePiece, 1994; V-659 (Box 1)
  - Hand's Up!: Gail Hand, Comedian/Actress, V-662 (Box 1)
  - El Celuloide Oculto, V-664 (Box 1)
  - Two in Twenty (Episodes 1 & 2), V-667 (Box 2)
  - Two in Twenty (Episodes 3 & 4), V-668 (Box 2)
  - Two in Twenty (Episode 5 & Outtakes), V-669 (Box 2)
  - Cynara: Poetry in Motion, V-670 (Box 2)
  - Straight Down the Aisle: Confessions of Lesbian Bridesmaids, V-672 (Box 2)
  - Lesbionage: A Romantic Detective Thriller, V-674 (Box 2)
  - Dyke TV: Volume V, V-654 (Box 1, ="box">1)
  - Dyke TV, 1993; V-690 (Box 3)
  - Dyke TV: The Best of Winter, 1994; V-691 (Box 4)
  - Changing Our Minds, V-709 (Box 4)
  - Brother Outsider, 2004; V-714 (Box 4)
  - Dyke TV, V-718 (Box 4)
  - Sex, Drugs & AIDS, 1987; V-719 (Box 4)
  - Seducin' a Sailor, 2001; V-727 (Box 4)
  - Limites, V-1115 (Box 4)
  - Diana's Hair Ego, V-5522 (Box 6)
  - The Trip, 2002; DVD-5 (Box 4)
  - Dangerous living: coming out in the developing world 2005, DVD-221 (Box 6)
  - Annie Sprinkle's Herstory of Porn, DVD-784 (Box 6)
  - A Very Natural Thing, V-6017 (Box 6)
  - You Are Not Alone, V-6018 (Box 6)
  - Mr. Angel, A Documentary by Dan Hun, DVD-1472 (Box 6)
  - Sacred Boy- Gay Sex Wisdom Volume 4, V-6142 (Box 8)
  - Carole Roussopoulos: A woman with her camera, DVD-2375
- Series VI. Miscellaneous
  - Archives Building Fund, video for the Lesbian Herstory Archives., V-665 (Box 2)
  - Betty Dodson: Selfloving, Video Portrait of a Women's Sexuality Seminar, V-673 (Box 2)
  - Thinking About Mental Health2: "Homosexuality: What Science Understands" and "Before Counseling Gays & Lesbians", V-680 (Box 3)
  - Suffer The Children: Answering the Homosexual Agenda in Public Schools by American Family Association 'Expose' on 'It's Elementary', from Brannan Street Editorial, San Francisco., V-720 (Box 4)
  - The bigger the better, pre-1995; V-725 (Box 4)
  - Daredevils, V-726 (Box 4)
  - Making it with Kristen Bjorn, 1999; V-728 (Box 4)
  - Speaking As A Woman with Alison Laing 1992, V-1456 (Box 6)
  - Basic Makeup Application with JoAnn Roberts, 1992; V-1457 (Box 6)
  - Art & Illusion, Tricks & Tips with JoAnn Roberts, 1993; V-1458 (Box 6)
  - LadyLike Deportment with Paula Sinclair, 1992; V-1459 (Box 6)
  - Ilbalsamatore = The Taxidermist, 2004; DVD-214 (Box 6)
  - Boondock Saints, 2001; DVD-222 (Box 6)
  - Video covers without the videos: Surfer Guys, Pleasure Beach, Shore Leave, Idol Country, and Brian's Men (Box 5)